http://www.betdevil.com/help/privacystatement/

---------------------------
Winner.com €25 Free Bet.
Help
MembershipGeneralInfo.
Login
Username:
Password:
Remember Me:
Analysis - Competitions
Copa Libertadores (1)
England Premier (1)
Spain La Liga (1)
Germany Bundesliga (1)
France Ligue 1 (1)
Italy Serie A (1)
Netherlands Eredivisie (1)
Russia Premier (1)
Algeria Ligue 1 (6)
Argentina Primera Nacional A (2)
Argentina Primera B Metropolitana
(2)
Argentina Primera C Metropolitana
(1)
Australia South Australia (1)
Austria 1 Liga (6)
Belgium Division 2 (1)
Belgium Pro League (1)
Bolivia Primera (3)
Brazil Serie B (4)
Bulgaria Parva Liga (1)
Bulgaria Vtora Liga (2)
1
2
3
4
»
Analysis - Date
Today (147)
Sat 12th (472)
Sun 13th (388)
Mon 14th (70)
Tue 15th (232)
Match List - Date
Tue 8th (145)
Wed 9th (168)
Thu 10th (89)
Today (147)
Sat 12th (472)
Sun 13th (388)
Mon 14th (70)
Tue 15th (232)
Match List - Competition
Copa Libertadores (1)
England Premier (12)
Spain La Liga (11)
Germany Bundesliga (13)
France Ligue 1 (10)
Italy Serie A (12)
Netherlands Eredivisie (9)
Russia Premier (8)
Brazil Serie A (10)
USA MLS (1)
England Championship (18)
Argentina Copa Liga Profesional (12)
Albania Superliga (5)
Algeria Ligue 1 (12)
Argentina Primera Nacional A (16)
Argentina Primera B Metropolitana
(9)
Argentina Primera C Metropolitana
(9)
Armenia Premier League (2)
Australia South Australia (1)
Austria 1 Liga (8)
9
»
4
»
Next 5 Days
Sponsored Links
WinnerGet a FREE €25 Bet. Money Back Promotions, Bonuses on Multiples.
PaddyPowerGet £50 Free Bet with PaddyPower. Money Back Specials, Justice Payouts and Early Payouts.
BetfairGet a FREE £50 Bet. Live Streaming on Major Sports. Try Cash Out in-play.
Privacy Policy for BetDevil.com
At BetDevil.com, accessible from our contact page, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by BetDevil.com and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
We are a Data Controller of your information.
BetDevil legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect the information:
BetDevil needs to perform a contract with you
You have given BetDevil permission to do so
Processing your personal information is in BetDevil legitimate interests
BetDevil needs to comply with the law
BetDevil will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies.
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.
The right of rectification.
The right to object.
The right of restriction.
The right to data portability
The right to withdraw consent
Log Files
BetDevil.com follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Like any other website, BetDevil.com uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information.
For more general information on cookies, please read "What Are Cookies".
Google DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Our Advertising Partners
Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.
Google
https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of BetDevil.com.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on BetDevil.com, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that BetDevil.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Party Privacy Policies
BetDevil.com's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Online Privacy Policy Only
Our Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in BetDevil.com. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Information Automatically Logged
BetDevil.com uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet.
Security
BetDevil.com receives personal data via online applications. These applications require private data and we therefore employ industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted browsers.
As no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you transfer the data at your own risk.
Message Boards/Chat Rooms/Forums
If you utilise a chat room or message board/forum operated by BetDevil.com, your use of those services is governed by the Terms and Conditions attaching to those services. If you choose to publish your email address or other personal data, you do so at your own risk.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.
BetDevil
Home
About Us
Benefits
Testimonials
Terms of Use
Privacy Statement
Membership
Go to Old Website
No Card required for Standard Membership.
BetDevil Limited, Letterkenny, Ireland. Reg No. 364542
Established : 2002
© Copyright 2002-2020, BetDevil. All Rights Reserved.
This is not a gambling or betting web site. We neither solicit nor accept bets. The information, stats, news and predictions on this web site are for the education and entertainment of its users only.
This website uses Necessary, Preferences, Statistics and Marketing cookies to provide our users with a comprehensive service.   Learn more
Accept   Reject
Rejecting the use of Necessary, Preferences, Statistics and Marketing cookies renders the site unusable.
Select 'Accept' to continue using the site or 'Reject' to leave the site.
Reject
